(Leonard:)Anyway, I'm not sure
she's the best fit
(Leonard:)for our little-- how should
we call it-- rebel alliance.
(Sheldon:)Oh, I never identified
with the rebel alliance.
(Sheldon:)Despite their tendency
to build Death Stars,
(Sheldon:)I've always been more
of an empire man.
(Leonard:)Yeah, not my point.
(Sheldon:)I know what your point is.
(Sheldon:)You're intimidated
by Amy's intellect.
(Sheldon:)To that I say, buck up.
(Leonard:)Okay, let me just
(Leonard:)get right to it.
(Leonard:)Amy is judgmental,
sanctimonious and frankly...
(Leonard:)just obnoxious.
(Sheldon:)So?
(Leonard:)So we already have
you for all that.
(Sheldon:)Are you suggesting I terminate
my relationship with Amy?
(Leonard:)No, no, of course not.
(Leonard:)Just have your relationship
someplace else.
(Sheldon:)May I point out that
for eight long months,
(Sheldon:)I suffered in silence
as your female companion
(Sheldon:)filled our apartment with her
(Sheldon:)off-key country music caterwauling,
(Sheldon:)the unappetizing spectacle
(Sheldon:)of her grinding a pumice stone
against her calloused feet